♪ We were good, we were gold ♪
♪ Kinda dream that can’t be
sold ♪
♪ We were right til we weren’t ♪
♪ Built a home and watched it
burn ♪
♪ I didn’t wanna leave you ♪
♪ I didn’t wanna lie ♪
♪ Started to cry but then
remembered I ♪
♪ I can buy myself flowers ♪
♪ Write my name in the sand ♪
♪ Talk to myself for hours ♪
♪ Say things you don’t
understand ♪
♪ I can take myself dancing ♪
♪ And I can hold my own hand ♪
♪ Yeah I can love me better than
you can ♪
♪ Can love me better ♪
♪ I can love me better baby ♪
♪ Paint my nails, cherry red ♪
♪ Match the roses that you left♪
♪ No remorse, no regret ♪
♪ I forgive every word you said♪
♪ I didn’t wanna wanna leave
you ♪
♪ I didn’t wanna fight ♪
♪ Started to cry but then
remembered I ♪
♪ I can buy myself flowers ♪
♪ Write my name in the sand ♪
♪ Talk to myself for hours ♪
♪ Say things you don’t
understand ♪
♪ I can take myself dancing ♪
♪ And I can hold my own hand ♪
♪ Yeah I can love me better than
you can ♪
♪ Can love me better ♪
♪ I can love me better baby ♪
♪ Can love me better, I ♪
♪ I didn’t wanna wanna leave
you ♪
♪ I didn’t wanna fight ♪
♪ Started to cry but then
remembered I ♪
♪ I can buy myself flowers ♪
♪ Write my name in the sand ♪
♪ Talk to myself for hours ♪
♪ Say things you don’t
understand ♪
♪ I can take myself dancing ♪
♪ And I can hold my own hand ♪
♪ Yeah I can love me better
than ♪
♪ Yeah I can love me better than
you can ♪
♪ Can love me better ♪
♪ I can love me better baby ♪
♪ Can love me better, I ♪